projecttimes.com 2019-09-03

# Project Management | privacy-policy

## PROJECT Times Privacy Policy

Project Times is sensitive to the privacy needs of its website visitors and members ("you" or "users").  This privacy policy applies to any personal information collected through this ProjectTimes.com website (the "Site") and discloses the privacy practices for all products and services of Project Times, a Macgregor Communications company (the "Company" or "we").

This privacy policy does not apply to other websites, including those that may be accessed through links contained on this Site.  This privacy policy does not apply to other online or offline activities of Advertisers, Sponsors, Partners, and/or Affiliates and does not apply to any information you supply to Company through any means other than this Site.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
The Company requires users to register for access to, or participation in certain parts of the Site, or to subscribe to certain products of the website such as email newsletters, online webinars, asset downloads such as whitepapers and templates, contests, polls, blogs, jobs, comments, and tell-a-friend, etc.  The company collects personal information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number to send notifications related to the Company's services. 

**Consent and Security**  
It is your choice whether or not you provide your registration information to the Company but registration information is required in order for the Company to provide you with services, namely, access to and/or participation in the Site.

The company also collects certain profile information in connection with the use of and participation in the social networking features of the Site.  This information includes, but is not limited to your company name, your title, your business interests and your geographic location, and is used for the purpose of assisting users in communicating with each other.

**Cookies and Log Files**  
The Site may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. Cookies can be used to provide you with tailored information from the Site.  You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.  The Site also records information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website, such as your Internet Protocol address.

The Site uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including web beacons.  Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites.  We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on the site, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of the Site.  These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf.  We may collect information from use of these technical methods in a form that is personally identifiable.

**Use of Personal Information**  
Certain User Profile information is displayed to people in order to facilitate the social network features of the Site.  The User Profile information that is publicly displayed is clearly marked as such in the registration process.   Email address are not publicly displayed as part of the User Profile nor are email addresses disclosed as part of peer to peer communication via the Site.

The Company may use email addresses to send information regarding the service, updates about the Site or Company newsletters.  Users may choose to stop receiving emails at any time by following the links contained within the emails to Unsubscribe.

**User-Generated Content** ****

Any material that you voluntarily post to publicly available blogs, forums, groups, message boards, comments, or any other public discussion areas can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.  You are solely responsible for the content of any material you post.

**Updating or Opting Out of the Service/Emails**  
Users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.  Users who do not wish to receive email notifications or email newsletters may opt out at any time by following the links contained within the emails to Unsubscribe.  
 ****

**How can you review, update, get a copy or delete your data?**  
You are free to review and update your information at any time directly through our site. To change your information please login to our site and click "My Account" link. If you want to delete or get a copy of your data on our site, send a mail to gdpr@macgregorcom.com . We will do that with immediate effect.

**How long does BA Times retain your information?**  
When you register for a BA Times account, we process and keep your personal data we have about you for as long as you don’t delete the account/unsubscribe yourself (subject to laws and regulations).

**Disclosure or Sharing of Information**  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, the Company will not disclose personal information to any third party unless you have opted in to recieve 3rd party information form our partners,  or we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Company, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Business Analyst Times.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Company reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Company or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.

If you have already opted into to receive 3rd party offers from our sponsors, you can unsubscribe by logging into your account and selecting NO to 3rd party partners.

**Use of Usage Information**  
Your usage information may be disclosed internally within the Company and in aggregated form to third parties.  For example, the Company may disclose usage information in order to better understand which parts of the Site users are visiting, to improve the content of the Site, and for marketing, advertising, or research purposes.

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**  
The Company may allow advertising services companies to serve advertisements within the Site.  Advertising may be based on usage, text, demographic, or other information gathered by or on behalf of the Company.  The Company's Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control, the activities of advertisers.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site operated by the Company, and not to any other websites to which the Site may link.

**Surveys and Contests**  
The Company may invite users to participate in surveys or contests.  User's participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary.  The information collected from surveys and contests may be used to identify aggregate demographic characteristics of users to improve our services, for marketing purposes, for industry reporting purposes, and/or to notify the winners and award prizes.  Subject to the user's preferences, such information also may be shared with third-party sponsors of such surveys or contests.

**What data breach procedures we have in place?**  
If in any case a breach of data such as loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure or access, personal data transmission, storage or otherwise processed happens, we will notify you immediately after we become aware of.

**Effective Date**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 7, 2007 and has been updated to comply with GDPR as of May 25, 2018, and will remain in effect unless changed.  The Company may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified Privacy Policy on the Site.

**Questions**  
You can get answers to your questions about our privacy policy, review your personal information, and correct inaccuracies by contacting Company through the Business Analyst Times website or by writing to: 

**Macgregor Communications c/o ProjectTimes.com**  
gdpr@macgregorcom.com   
110 Cochrane Dr., Unit 1  
Markham, Ontario  
L3R 9S1  
Canada
